fidocastingcall.ca 2013-05-11

# Privacy Policy | Fido.ca

|   
---  
  
| 

## Website Terms and Conditions

  * Use of Web Site Policy
  * YouTube Comment Policy
  * Fido Facebook Comment Policy
  * Fido Google+ Page Comment Policy
  * Pinterest Engagement Guidelines

## Fido Service Terms and Conditions

  * Fido Terms and Conditions
  * Acceptable Use Policy
  * Arbitration Protocol
  * Privacy Policy
  * FidoREWARDS Program Terms and Conditions
  * FidoTRADE™ Terms and Conditions
  * Fido Device Protection Plan Terms and Conditions
  * _Fido TechXpert™_ Terms and Conditions
  * Get to know Fido Guide

Privacy Policy

  1. This policy applies to Fido Solutions, operated by Rogers Communications Partnership, which is referred to here as Fido. At Fido, the security and integrity of our customers' personal information is important to us. We take every reasonable measure necessary to protect the privacy of our customers while providing the high level communication services they expect.

  2. Fido’s privacy practices are in accordance with all federal and provincial laws and regulations. We are compliant with the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act and where applicable with the privacy rules established by the Canadian Radio-television and Telecommunications Commission.

  3. At Fido, we collect customer information for one or more of the following purposes:

    * To provide a positive customer experience, and deliver, bill for, and collect payment for products and services;

    * To understand customer requirements and make information available regarding products and services offered by Fido directly or through its network of distributors, and its related companies, including the Rogers group of companies;

    * To manage and develop Fido’s business and operations;

    * To meet legal and regulatory requirements; and

    * To obtain credit information or provide it to others.

  4. Fido does not use or disclose personal information for purposes other than those for which it was collected, except with the consent of the individual or as required by law. Fido retains personal information only as long as necessary for the fulfilment of those purposes.

  5. Fido informs customers of the existence, use and disclosure of their personal information upon request and gives them access to their information.

  6. Fido ensures that customer information is accurate, complete and up-to-date. Customers can challenge the accuracy and completeness of the information and request amendments as appropriate.

  7. Fido shares information with other Fido related companies, including the Rogers companies, in order to offer customers products and services that they may find attractive. Notices on sharing information are contained on Fido’s invoice and on fido.ca. If customers do not want to be marketed with these products and services, they can contact Fido at 1-888-481-3436.

  8. A senior company officer has been appointed as the Privacy Officer. The Privacy Officer is accountable for all personal information at Fido. To contact the Privacy Officer or file a complaint, write to:

> Chief Privacy Officer  
>  Fido Solutions  
>  800 De La Gauchetière Street West  
>  Suite 4000  
>  Montréal, Quebec  
>  H5A 1K3  
> 

  9. Customers that wish to obtain:

    * more information about this Commitment to Privacy;

    * access to, or more information about, their personal information held by Fido; or

    * make a privacy-related complaint; may contact a Fido customer service representative who, if necessary, will refer the customer to the Fido Privacy Officer.

Top of page  
  
---
